A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1994-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- IV. Assigned State Agencies, 1994-2006., Extent: 16.10 cubic feet (20 boxes). (Box 60-79)
  - Correspondence from State Agencies
    - Virginia Economic Development Partnership
      - International Trade, 2002-2003 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - Kilduff Compensation, 2003-2004 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - Marketing and International Trade, 2003-2004 (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Marketing Initiatives, 2002-2003 (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - Non Bank Financial Services, 2002-2003 (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - Norfolk Southern (Hampton Roads Region), 2002 (Box 69, Folder 17)
      - Operating Plan (Proposed), 2002 (Box 69, Folder 18)
      - Operating Plan (Proposed), 2005 (Box 69, Folder 19)
      - Operating Plan, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 20)
      - Operating Plan (Proposed), 2005-2006 (Box 69, Folder 21)
      - Personnel Committee Meeting, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 22)
      - Presentation, 2002-2003 (Box 69, Folder 23)
      - Project Emily, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 24)
      - Project Emmitt, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 25)
      - Project Ring, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 26)
      - Annual Reports, 2002-2004 (Box 69, Folder 27)
      - Annual Report, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 28)
      - Report, Employment Creation and Capital Investment, 2002 and 2004 (Box 69, Folder 29)
      - Expenditure Report for Fiscal Year Ended June 30, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 30)
      - Expendiure Report for Fiscal Year Ended June 30, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 31)
      - Report on Business Incentives, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 32)
      - Report on Business Incentives, 2002-2003 (Box 69, Folder 33)
      - Report on Business Incentives, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 34)
      - Report-Southwest Virginia Air Freight Feasibility Study, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 35)
      - Report-Taking VEDP Forward, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 36)
      - Report to the VEDP Board of Directors, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Virginia is for Business Annual Report, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Retreat Meeting, 2002-2004 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Return on Investment, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Specialty Blades, Inc., 2005 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - State Unemployment Tax Avoidance (SUTA), 2003 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Institute for Advanced Learning and Research, undated (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Virgin Air, 2003-2004 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Virginia Defense and Homeland Security, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Virginia Defense and Homeland Security Industry, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Virginia Defense and Homeland Security Industry, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Virginia Defense and Homeland Security Industry, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Virginia Defense and Homeland Security Industry, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - Virginia Economic Overview, 2003-2004 (Box 70, Folder 14)
      - Asian Trade Mission, 2003-2004 (Box 70, Folder 15)
      - Asian Trade Mission (Japan and Korea), 2003 (Box 70, Folder 16)
      - Asian Trade Mission (Japan, Korea and China), 2003 (Box 70, Folder 17)
      - Asian Trade Mission-Postponed, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 18)
      - British Trade Mission, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 19)
      - Boston Region Trade Mission, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 20)
      - British Embassy Visit, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 21)
      - Cuba Trade Mission, 2002-2004 (Box 70, Folder 22)
      - Cuba-Newsletter, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 23)
      - Detroit Trade Mission, 2002-2003 (Box 70, Folder 24)
      - European Trade Mission, 2002-2003 (Box 70, Folder 25)
      - European Trade Mission, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 26)
      - Germany Trade Mission, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 27)
      - Governor Warner's Trade Mission to Europe, 2003 May 18-24, Trip Book (Box 70, Folder 28)
      - India Trade Mission, 2004-2005 (Box 70, Folder 29)
      - Japan Trade Mission, 2002-2003 (Box 70, Folder 30)
      - Japan and India Trade Mission, 2005 (Box 70, Folder 31)
      - Korea, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 32)
      - Mexico Trade Mission, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 33)
      - New York Trade Mission, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 34)
      - Private Sector Trade Mission, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 35)
      - Trade Mission Dates, 2004-2005 (Box 70, Folder 36)
      - San Francisco Trade Mission, 2002-2003 (Box 70, Folder 37)
      - Saudi Arabia, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 38)
    - Virginia Employment Commission
      - Coal Miners Retraining, 2004 (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Coordinated Economic Relief Center, 2002-2005 (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - Customer Call Center, 2002-2004 (Box 63, Folder 13)
      - Dept. of General Services, 1994-2002 (Box 63, Folder 14)
      - General Correspondence, undated (Box 63, Folder 15)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 January-May (Box 63, Folder 16)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 June-September (Box 63, Folder 17)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 October-November (Box 63, Folder 18)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 January-March (Box 63, Folder 19)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 April-July (Box 63, Folder 20)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 August-December (Box 63, Folder 21)
      - General Correspondence, 2004 January-August (Box 63, Folder 22)
      - General Correspondence, 2004 September-December (Box 63, Folder 23)
      - General Correspondence, 2005 March-May (Box 63, Folder 24)
      - General Correspondence, 2005 June-December and 2006 January (Box 63, Folder 25)
      - Governor's Economic Crisis Task Force, Correspondence, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 26)
      - Miner Survey, undated (Box 63, Folder 27)
      - New Balance Proposal, 2002-2003 (Box 63, Folder 28)
      - Report on Audit, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 29)
      - Restructuring, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 30)
      - Virginia Employment Commission Act, 2001-2002 (Box 63, Folder 31)
      - Virginia Workforce System Policy, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 32)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority
      - Family Rule, 2002-2003 (Box 62, Folder 21)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 22)
      - General Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 62, Folder 23)
      - Low Income Tax Credit, 2001-2002 (Box 62, Folder 24)
      - Low Income Tax Credit, 2003-2005 (Box 62, Folder 25)
      - Multi Family Housing Bonds, 2000-2003 (Box 62, Folder 26)
      - Rental Housing Bonds, 1999-2001 (Box 62, Folder 27)
      - Rental Housing Bonds, 2002-2003 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Rental Housing Bonds, 2004-2005 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Report-Financial Statements and Accompanying Schedules, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Report-Management's Discussion and Analysis, 2002-2003 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Report-Management's Discussion and Analysis, 2003-2004 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Report-Resource Allocation Study, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Report-The Genesis Project, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Single Family Housing Authority Bonds, 1998-2000 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Single Family Housing Authority Bonds, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Single Family Housing Authority Bonds, 2002-2005 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Racing Commission
      - General Correspondence, 2001-2005 (part one) (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence, 2001-2005 (part two) (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Racing Commission Study, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Colonial Downs, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Colonial Downs, 1994-1999 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Racetrack License, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Virginia Jockey Club vs. Virginia Racing Commission, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Resources Authority
      - General Correspondence, 2001-2005 (part one) (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence, 2001-2005 (part two) (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Infrastructure Revenue Bonds, 2001-2005 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Briefings, 2002-2003 (part one) (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Briefings, 2002-2003 (part two) (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous, 2002-2005 (part one) (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous, 2002-2005 (part two) (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous, 2002-2005 (part three) (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission
      - Audited Financial Statements, 2004 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Economic Indicator's for Virginia's Tobacco Producing Communities, undated (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Education Grant Workforce Services, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 January-April (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 May-August (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 September-December (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 January-April (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 June-October (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 September-November (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - General Correspondence, 2004 January-December (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - General Correspondence, 2005 January-November (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Grant Program, 2003-2004 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Grant Guidelines, 2002-2005 (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Meeting Materials, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - Meeting Materials, 2005 August 16-18 (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - Meeting Materials, 2005 November 10 (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - Member Contact Information, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - Regional Finance Workgroups, 2005 (Box 71, Folder 18)
      - Report-Proposal for an Advanced Telecommunications Network in Southern Virginia, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 19)
      - Report-Proposal for the Virginia Tobacco Commission, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 20)
      - Report-Heart of Appalachia Tourism Authority, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 21)
      - Report on the Comparative Revenue Capacity, Revenue Effort, and Fiscal Stress of Virginia's Counties and Cities 2002/2003, April 2005 (Box 71, Folder 22)
      - Report-Smyth-Washington Regional Industrial Facilities Authority Workforce Training Study, 2004 (Box 71, Folder 23)
      - Report-Virginia Institute for Performance Engineering and Research Business Plan, 2004 (Box 71, Folder 24)
      - Southside Economic Development Commission, 2003-2004 (Box 71, Folder 25)
      - Southside Economic Development Committee Meeting, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 26)
      - Southside Economic Development Committee Meeting, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 27)
      - Southside Economic Development Committee Meeting, 2003 October 21 (Box 71, Folder 28)
      - Southside Economic Development Committee Meeting, Wise County, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 29)
      - Southside Economic Development Committee, 2003-2005 (Box 71, Folder 30)
      - Southside Economic Development Committee Meeting, 2005 (Box 71, Folder 31)
      - Southside Economic Development Commission, 2005 (Box 71, Folder 32)
      - Soutside and Southwest Economic Development, 2005 (Box 71, Folder 33)
      - Southside Technology, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 34)
      - Southside Value-Added Beef Initiative, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 35)
      - Special Projects Funds, 2002-2003 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Special Projects Funds, 2002-2003 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Special Projects Funds, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Special Projects Funds, 2002-2003 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Special Projects Funds Committee Meeting, 2004 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Applications for Special Projects Funds, 2002-2003 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Special Projects, Southside Business Initiative, undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Tobacco Securitization, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Tobacco Securitization, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Tobacco Securitization, 2002-2003 (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Tobacco Securitization, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Tobacco Securitization, 2005 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Tobacco Securitization, A.L. Philpott Southside Economic Development Commission, HJR 300, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Tobacco Securitization, Settlement Securitization-Update, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - Tobacco Securitization, TICR Spending and Endowment Analysis, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 15)
      - Tobacco Securitization, Tobacco Settlement Financing Information, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 16)
      - Strategic Investment Director Position, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 17)
      - Strategic Investment Director Position, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 18)
      - Strategic Investment Director Position, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 19)
      - Technology Committee Presentation (Mid-Atlantic Broadband Cooperative), 2005 (Box 72, Folder 20)
      - Tobacco Board Members, 2004 (Box 72, Folder 21)
      - Virginia's Electric Cooperative Living Magazine, 2004 (Box 72, Folder 22)
      - Virginia Tobacco Commission Planning Session and Committee Meeting, 2004 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Tourism Corporation
      - General Correspondence, 2001-2006 (part one) (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence, 2001-2006 (part two) (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence, 2001-2006 (part three) (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, 2001-2006 (part four) (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence, 2001-2006 (part five) (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - PLAYTONE/John Adams, 2005 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous Reports and Brouchures, 2004 and undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous Reports and Brouchures, 2002 and undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous Reports and Brouchures, undated (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous Reports and Brouchures, 2002-2005 and undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Community Resource Guide for Brownfields Redevelopment (Second Edition), 2002 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Reports and Meeting Notes, 2002-2003 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Virginia Film Office, 2001-2004 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Virginia Dept. of Transportation, 2003 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Rails to Trails, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Governor's Outdoor Resources Panel, 2003 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Board of Directors' Meeting, 2004 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Budget, 2003 and 2005 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - 2005 Tourism Report (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Jamestown 2007, 1998-2005 (part one) (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Jamestown 2007, 1998-2005 (part two) (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Jamestown 2007, 1998-2005 (part three) (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Small, Women and Minority Owned (SWAM) Procurement
      - Communication Strategy, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence, February-May 2004 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence, March-May 2004 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence, September-November 2004 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Inter-Secretarial SWAM Procurement Task Force Reports, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - Model Supplier Diversity Plan, July 2002 (Box 79, Folder 8)
      - Procurement Disparity of the Commonwealth of Virginia-Final Report, January 2004 (Box 79, Folder 9)
      - Procurement Disparity of the Commonwealth of Virginia-Final Report, January 2004 (Box 79, Folder 10)
      - Procurement Disparity of the Commonwealth of Virginia-Final Report, January 2004 (Box 79, Folder 11)
      - Procurement Disparity of the Commonwealth of Virginia-Final Report, January 2004 (Box 79, Folder 12)
      - Report of the Governor's Advisory Commission on Minority Business Enterprise, November 2003 (Box 79, Folder 13)
      - Higher Education SWAM Analysis, 2003-2005, September 2005 (Box 79, Folder 14)
      - VDOT Utilization and Availability Study, March 2004 (Box 79, Folder 15)
      - VA Partner in Procurement, 2003-2004 (Box 79, Folder 16)
      - Vendor Premium Report, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 17)
- V. Advisory Boards, Councils and Commissions, 1998-2005., Extent: 2.35 cubic feet (3 boxes). (Box 80-82)
  This series is composed of files pertaining to various boards, councils, commissions and projects with which the Office of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade was involved, both inside and outside the Secretariat. The files contain correspondence, e-mail, memorandums, notes, presentation, reports, and other working documents. The series is housed in 3 boxes and is arranged alphabetically.
  Notable subjects include: American Civil War Center in Richmond; Virginia's attempts to lure a Major League Baseball team to the Commonwealth (Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority); development and implementation of Governor Warner's Biotechnology Initiative; and the development of Governor Warner's Workforce Initiative.
  - American Civil War Center
    - Audio Visual Program Treatments for the American Civil War Center at Historic Tredegar, 22 April 2005 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Exhibit Planning, 2005 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - News Articles, 2005 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2001-2003 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, Meeting of the Board of Directors, Briefing Material, 25 February 2005 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Asian Advisory Board
    - General Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority
    - Annual Report, 1998-2000 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Ballpark Development in the 1990s, 12 November 1998 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Ballpark Financing Plan, MZ Sports, LLC, 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Baseball Meeting, New York, 2001-2003 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Economic and Fiscal Impacts of a Major League Baseball Franchise and Stadium on the Commonwealth of Virginia, by George Mason University, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - E-mail Support Documentation, 2002-2003 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Major League Baseball in Northern Virginia: Transcending the Game, May 2003 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Options for Financing Current Operations of the Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Status Report on Baseball, Emerging Business Forum and 2012 Olympics, 2 January 2002 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Baseball Club, McGuire Woods, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Baseball Handbook for the Virginia General Assembly, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Briefing Book, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Presentation to the Virginia Baseball Stsdium Authority Finance Committee, 27 September 2002 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Initiative
    - Biotechnology Macro Partnership Facility, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - E-Mail (Policy Discussions), 2002 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - E-Mail (Policy Discussions), 2003 (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - E-Mail (Policy Discussions), 2004 (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - E-Mail (Policy Discussions), 2005 (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Executive Order No. 14 (2002) The Virginia Biotechnology Initiative (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Signs of Life: The Growth of Biotechnology Centers in the U.S., 2002 (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Governor's Advisory Board, 2002-2003 (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Bio-Initiatives Legislative Overview, undated (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - Memorandums, 2002-2005 (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - News Articles, 2002-2004 (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - North Carolina Biotechnology Center, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Northern Virginia Biotech Facility Proposal, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Pamphlet: Advancing New York's Leadership Role in Medical Research and Biotechnology, undated (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - Personal Observations from Advisory Board Member Dan Gonzalez, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 36)
    - Presentations, 2002-2004 (Box 80, Folder 37)
    - Property Site, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 38)
    - Publications, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 39)
    - Recommendations for a Statewide Comprehensive and Coordinated Strategy for Biotech, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 40)
    - Final Report of the Governor's Commission on Biotechnology, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Report: Grown New Business with Seed and Venture Capital, 2000 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Intellectual Property Task Force Report, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Phase II Interim Report: A Leadership Strategy and Budget Recommendations to Provide the Resources, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Report: Recommendations for a Statewide Comprehensive and Coordinated Strategy for Biotechnology, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Understanding CAPCOs, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Biotech Initiatives Board Members and Contacts, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Biotech: Vision 2010, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Biotechnology Summit, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Written Notes, 2002-2003 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - National Governors' Association
    - A Governor's Guide to Creating a 21st Century Workforce, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Initiatives, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Other States' Workforce Projects, 2001-2002 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Report: Occupational Demand and Supply by Industry Cluster and Region, 2002-2003 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Shipbuilding, undated (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Workforce Academy, 2002-2004 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Workforce Academy Core Group, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Workforce Academy Home Team, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Workforce Investment Act Policy, 2002-2004 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Worforce Policy Academy Development, 2003-2005 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Virginia Advanced Shipbuilding and Carrier Integration Center Board
    - Records, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Economic Developers Association
    - Records, 2003-2004 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Hungary, 2003-2004 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Workforce Council
    - Records, 2002-2005 (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Career and Educatonal Development for Workforce, 2002-2004 (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums, 2002-2005 (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Demand Planning, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Greenville Workforce Center, 2004-2005 (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - Implenmentation Panel for House Bill 1954 and Senate Bill 1058, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - Memorandum of Understanding with Virginia Community College System and Virginia Employemnt Commission, 2003-2005 (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - Migrant and Seasonal Farm Workers Board, 2002-2004 (Box 81, Folder 33)
    - Power Point Presentation: Virginia's Resource for Employers' Workforce, undated (Box 81, Folder 34)
    - Power Point Presentation: Strategic Planning Session, undated (Box 81, Folder 35)
    - Power Point Presentation: Workforce Development Trends, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 36)
    - Rapid Response, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 37)
    - Demonstration Project Proposal: Richmond One-Stop Career Center System Design, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 38)
    - WorkKeys: The Language for Building a Career Development System, undated (Box 81, Folder 39)
    - Resource Map-Funding Summary 2004, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 40)
    - Resumes, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 41)
    - Strategic Plan, 2002 and 2005 (Box 81, Folder 42)
    - Strategic Planning Session, 7-8 June 2005 (Box 81, Folder 43)
    - Virginia Workforce Network, 2002 and 2005 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Workforce Investment Act, 2002-2005 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Workforce Investement Area Board, 2002-2005 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Workforce Investment Area Community Profile VII, undated (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Workforce Investment Area Statistical Measures, 2003-2005 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Workforce Matrix, 2002-2003 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Workforce Training, 2002-2003 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- VI. Development Projects and Initiatives Files, 2001-2005., Extent: 6.25 cubic feet (16 boxes). (Box 83-98)
  This series is housed in 16 boxes and is divided into 2 sections: alphabetical and regional. This series documents the projects and initiatives of the Secretary's office relating to development.